http://www.canadianflight.org/content/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting the Canadian Museum of Flight website. The Museum does not collect personal information about visitors to our website unless you choose to provide that information to us. The Museum does not sell, exchange, or release your personal information to parties outside the Museum without your consent.
The Canadian Museum of Flight website will only collect personal information which you knowingly and voluntarily provide by, for example, sending emails, completing membership forms, registering for events, or ordering merchandise. If you provide us with personal information, we will normally respond to your inquiry, request, or order. We may also contact you to provide information about Museum activities, programs, membership and development opportunities, products, and special events that may interest you. We will never share your name or information outside the Museum unless you authorize us to do so.
Copyright Policy
All Canadian Museum of Flight web pages and content are under copyright of the Museum. All banners, icons, logos and original graphics on the Canadian Museum of Flight Web site are also under copyright of the Museum and may not be used for any purpose.
Book A Tour
Facebook
Twitter
YouTube
Search
DonateAviation LinksPrivacy PolicyJoin the TeamGift ShopSitemapAviation HistoryContact UsCultural Access PassFundraisingKids SectionPressSponsorsTechTalk
Help Us Soar - Donate to the Museum
Copyright © 2008 Canadian Museum of Flight. All rights reserved.Web design by Acro Media Inc
